Hello Hello I'm from the city of
Здравствуйте Здраствуйте Я из города
Khmelnitsky Where are you from? I'm from Moscow,
Хмельницкий Вы откуда Я с Москвы пря
just a native or someone who
именно коренной или
went there, my mother lived here, my grandmother lived here, she
поехавший мама тут жила бабушка жила де
lived there, and Bausch lived there too, as far as I know. As far as I know, I do
жи бауш тоже Т жила насколько я знаю А
n't know who the nationality is, there's a lot
по национальности кто не знаю там много
mixed up with my dad's roots, they're Germans, my mom
намешано у папы по корням там немцы мама
[music]
[музыка]
that the whole question was never
ев что все вопрос никогда не
raised, I understood and the World Cup is communicating here Yes, I don’t
поднимали понял а ЧМ тут общаетесь Да не
know, I just logged in less than 5 minutes even
знаю я только зашёл меньше 5 минут даже
passed In general, this is the first time in Tet Roulette
прошло Вообще первый раз в тет рулетке у
you haven’t had this before, the last time was about
вас нет так до этого я последний раз
two months, probably two months Why are you
месяца два наверно месяца два Да чём вы
communicating with Lumi Yes, just  about anything Anything about
общаетесь с Люми Да просто о всяком О
any general topics
чём получится какие-то либо общие темы
or someone has something interesting he
либо у кого-то что-то интересное есть он
can tell, I’ll listen to him What are the
может рассказать я его послушаю е какие
general topics Name your topics now we’ll
общие темы Называйте свои темы сейчас мы
hire the intersection of many of our topics yuzhi
найм пересечение множест наших тем южи
just there what a person is interested in what
просто там чем человек увлекается что
what  he’s interested in life In general,
что по жизни ему интересно В целом
maybe he
какие-то Может у него увлечения
has some unusual hobbies, yeah, and here I am, a
необычные есть там Угу И вот я я полтора
year and a half ago, like, well, I fell in love with cinema,
года назад типа ну полюбил кинематограф
so it’s an interesting topic, maybe they haven’t watched
так интересная тема может не смотрели
the director Robert Madyar, there is
режиссёр Роберт мадяр есть
one What kind of films does he have, he has
такой Какие картины у него есть у него
action films Well, this is an elastic concept  Well,
боевики Ну это понятие растяжимое Ну
for example, Well, it’s
например Ну что-нибудь
possible that it was rumored that it wasn’t the TV series
возможно что на слуху там было не сериал
Jaga, I
джага
didn’t haven’t heard it, although considering how many
не не слышал учи Хотя учитывая сколько
TV series there are now,
сейчас сериалов
it’s basically normal that I
это это в принципе нормально что это
don’t recognize this name. That is, Robert
название не узнаю Вот то есть Роберт
Madyar, he’s like a Ukrainian director, he’s
мадяр он как бы украинский режиссёр он
from Transcarpathia himself, that’s it  closer to
сам из Закарпатья это вот ближе к
Hungary So I don’t know if he’s either a Wenger or a
Венгрии Так я не знаю он или Венгер или
Ukrainian by nationality, but his
украинец по национальностью но у него
name is Robert and his surname is May not his
звать его Роберт и фамилия мая не
surname there Godi but Madyar is his like a
фамилия там годи а мадяр его как
director’s stage image so yes
режиссёрский сценический образ такой да
Robert is Madyar and he produces and redirects he is both a
Роберт мадяр и он продюсирует и ресет он
producer and director Yes of the series  Jaga
и продюсер и режиссёр Да сериала джага
Jaga makes such
джага там вот снимает такие
adventure
приключенческие
short films there, for example, I
короткое фильмы например вот мне
remember the hunt for ninjas, for example,
запомнилась охота на ниндзю например вот
there when they hunted ninjas from a quadcopter,
там когда с квадрокоптера на ниндзю
like, well, surrealism, like a
охотились типа ну така сюрреализм типа
modern interesting way, okay,
современный интересный способ ладно да
yes, that is, I advise you to look on
Вот то есть я советую Посмотрите на
Google, Robert Madyar Jaga Jaga,
гуглите Роберт мадяр джага джага
sign up for
запишитесь
Ravi
Рави
Dagu  in that case, then I can
дагу в таком случае Тогда я вам могу
recommend a series to you. A good one is called
посоветовать сериал Хороший называется
darkness, a German series is absolutely wonderful. Yeah, you
тьма немецкий сериал прямо замечательный
need to think a little bit in some
Угу чуть-чуть нужно думать в некоторых
moments, but in general, what is
моментах но так в целом а О чём о чём
this series about? Well, in short, you
этот сериал Ну если коротко то вот
know, there is the Grandfather Paradox or the
знаете есть Парадокс дедушки или
Beat
Парадокс бит
Hover Paradox.  It’s called, well, let’s say you
ховера он называется ну допустим вы
go back to the past, kill your
возвращаетесь в прошлое убиваете своего
grandfather, you’re not born, but since you’re
дедушку вы не рождаетесь Но поскольку Вы
not born, you don’t go back in time, you
не рождаетесь вы не попадаете в прошлое
don’t kill your grandfather, so you’re
не убиваете дедушку соответственно вы
alive, and if you’re alive, you go back to the
живы а если вы живы возвращаетесь в
past, that’s roughly speaking. Listen,
прошлое вот это вот грубо говоря Слушай
Robert Mandr also has Well, plots
у Роберта Мандра тоже есть Ну сюжеты
that  echo this there,
которые перекликаются с этим там
for example, uh, dude, yes, in short,
например э чувак да вот короче он
he, uh, goes to the army, he is sent to a
э идёт типа в армию его отправляют в
foreign country. There, to kill him, in short, they kill him
чужую страну Там убивать его короче
and he returns in a black
убивают и он возвращается в чёрном
bag, and the paradox is that if
пакете и вот парадокс в том что если бы
he had not gone to kill, Yes, he would not have returned
он не пошёл убивать Да он бы не вернулся
to  in the black bag, there’s a very interesting
в чёрном пакете вот там очень интересная
connection there, well, right here, it’s a
такая взаимосвязь ну здесь прямо это
good series, it’s on Netflix,
хороший сериал там он он на нетфликсе
and it’s essentially like that, and
выходит и там по сути такие и
time travel, you
путешествия во времени чуть-чуть
need to think a little, and tragedies and dramas, to
подумать нужно и трагедии и драмы в
some extent, even a little comedy. Yes,
какой-то степени даже чуть комедии Есть
he has.  there is also such surrealism like
Угу У него ещё там такой сюрреализм типа
uh The thing is that he combines action films
ээ Дело в том что он комбинирует боевики
with horror films Yes, he has this
с ужастиками Да вот у него есть это
uh there the characters are called worms
ээ там персонажи такие черви называются
Yes And in Ukrainian it’s hrobak it’s
Да И вот по-украински это хробак оно вот
in Russian if it sounds like worms Yes and in
по-русски если звучить то черви Да и
short there are worms like  they attack people,
короче там черви типа они атакуют людей
but in short, he’s a positive hero, he’s kind of
вот а Короче позитивный герой он типа
attacking these worms, in short, there’s such a
атакует этих червей короче там такая
weird theme, like, but damn the worms there, in short, in
стрёмная тема типа но блин червей там
different ways, these
выпалить короче по-разному типа этих
worms are very interesting, well, it’s like an
червей очень интересно ну как бы на
amateur, an amateur, yes, but it’s not an
любителя на любителя Да филь но на
amateur, that doesn’t mean that it’s  bad
любителя это не значит что это плохой
because sometimes even for an amateur it
потому что иногда и на любитель
turns out to be good not very good
оказывается хороши не очень хороший
very good Yes, he is the director
очень хороший Да он вот это режиссёр
Robert he on he first started releasing
Робер он на он сначала начал выпускать
it without a budget Yes this is not Hollywood he
это ж без бюджета Да это не Голливуд он
started filming like that then uh he gained
начал снимать так потом ээ получил
enormous popularity at least
огромную популярность по крайней мере
among our people I don’t  I know, or they watch him abroad en
среди нашей я не знаю или за границ его
masse Yes, but here he
там массово смотрят Да но у нас он
gained popularity and he began to collect
получил популярность и он начал собирать
for his films. That is, he says
на свои фильмы То есть он говорит вот
there is a collection for
есть сбор на
uh equipment for new films, like yes,
ээ аппаратуру для новых фильмов типа да
people give him, in short, 3 million Greens per day,
люди ему короче за день там 3 млн Грин
for example, they throw off something like this  uh in dollars
например скидывают типа это э в долларах
s How long does it take in short, almost
с Сколько получается короче почти там
100,000 dollars, that is, they
100.000 долларов да то есть за день
spend a day on equipment for new
скидывают на аппаратуру для новых
films, you know, so he makes
фильмов понимаешь Вот и он и делает
new films, he recruits these
новые фильмы он набирает этих там
new actors, he recruits uh operators
актёров новых набирает ээ операторов
who film there, in short, a bunch of a bunch of
которые там снимают короче куча куча
types of workers Well, basically
типа работников Ну в принципе шанс
he probably has a chance to get to
наверное у него есть добраться до
something high, yes he gets to something high,
чего-то высокого да до чего-то высо
that’s how he would say Previously,
добирается вот как бы он скажем Раньше
he had a small plot, now there
он э маленький сюжет сейчас уже такие
are such full-fledged ones, you know, he used to
полноценные там есть знаешь вот он
make short films of 2-3 minutes
раньше короткометражки делал 2-3 минуты
such you know, uh plots are usually usually
такие знаешь ээ сюжети обычно обычно с
that’s where they always start with a short
этого и начинают всегда с коротки
footage, then they grow further,
метража потом уже вырастают дальше
now even it’s shorter, it’s there for 15
теперь даже он есть короче иде там по 15
minutes and you see, like, it
минут и ты смотришь понимаешь типа вот
seems to you that there are Ninja worms in short,
тебе кажется там черви Ниндзя короче
some kind of cameraman What the hell is this nonsense, you’re having a blast
оператор какой-то Что за бред да ты
You’re so immersed in the
кайфуешь Ты настолько погружаешься в
filming Well  the director is so talented, uh, I
съёмку Ну настолько таланте режиссёр ээ
don’t know who writes the script, he keeps
не знаю кто пишет сценарий вот держит он
it a secret, yes, but he does the directing, he has
это в секрете да но режиссура занимается
editors, yes, it turns out that
он монтажёры есть у него да получается
these are the ones who make the final
вот эти ну которые делают конечный
product Yes, it’s like they have this, how to
продукт Да он как бы у них этот как
say Well, as a director, he kind of
сказать Ну как режиссёр он типа
plans it says there  this is we let these
планирует говорит там это пускаем эти
shots into production these we don’t
кадры в продакшн эти не
let okay interesting
пускаем окей интересно
yes good run Yes remember Robert ban
да хорошо побегу Да запомните Роберт бан
jaga jaga
джага джага
ofi
офи
write nay Telegram right now axis VN
пись най Telegram прям зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more politely YouTube keeping
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us busy through skarg or in your ban and even more
нас через скарг ор в твий бан и дуже
richly I don’t show the video to people  Sometimes we don’t
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams for
показуе информация про стримы тому для
you, we Mali operational link to write
тоб мы Мали оперативный звязок пишиться
directly at the same time and while there in telegram okm
прямо зараз а пок там в телеграми окм
video schezh tsikava and korisna information
видео ще теж цикава и корисна информация
and we are guilty of you trimati postiyny
и мы повинни з вами тримати постийний
operational link
оперативный звязок
independantly in that chi show you about it
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
write
пись